{
    "subject": "resource/Key_Largo_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "resource/Jerry_Wald",
    "human_readable": "The producer of Key Largo (film) is Jerry Wald.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9177679419517517,
            "question": "Who produced the film Key Largo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8891602158546448,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Jerry Wald."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8748225569725037,
            "question": "Is Jerry Wald known for producing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8568958044052124,
            "question": "What is the name of the film produced by Jerry Wald?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7509062886238098,
            "question": "What other films might Jerry Wald have produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5685910582542419,
            "question": "What genre is the film Key Largo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5085832476615906,
            "question": "What makes Key Largo a memorable film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3891572952270508,
            "question": "Where was Key Largo filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37274086475372314,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in Key Largo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3545420467853546,
            "question": "What year was Key Largo released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of Key Largo (film) is Jerry Wald.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3224_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in Key Largo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3224_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Key Largo filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3224_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Key Largo a memorable film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3224_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3224_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3224_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3224_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3224_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3224_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3224_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3224_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3224_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3224_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3224_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions that \"Jerry Wald produced such films as \u2018Key Largo\u2019 (1948)\", which supports the statement that Jerry Wald was the producer of the film \"Key Largo\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}